go2convert.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Go2convert.com

## Privacy Policy

**Go2Convert.com** created this privacy statement to illustrate our company commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information collecting and cookies for Go2Convert.com.

**Collecting of Personally-Identifying Information  
**When a visitor joins Go2Convert.com as our member, certain personality-identifying information is requested. For example, username, email address, website name and website URL. Go2Convert.com collects such information just to fulfill the purpose of visitor's interaction and shall never sell or trade such information with others. Go2Convert.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Go2Convert.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of www.phpkode.com, third parties, or the public at large. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Go2Convert.com uses cookies to help Go2Convert.com identify and track visitors, their usage of www.get-simple.info website, and their website access preferences. Visitors can set browsers to refuse cookies place on their computers, but certain features of Go2Convert.com may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**   
Advertising partners may set cookies when their ads appeared on Go2Convert.com to allow ad server to recognize your computer. The aim of these cookies is to illustrate targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Go2Convert.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Security**   
To protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control, log file access is restricted to system administrators only once stored on Go2Convert.com server.

**Contact Information**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us at editor(at)iKode.com.

Recent Posts

IMG to JPEG IMG can be converted to JPEG with our online converter. This online converter is free for every body.

PSD to JPEG PSD can be converted to JPEG with our online converter. This online converter is free for every body.

CR2 to JPEG CR2 can be converted to JPEG with our online converter. This online converter is free for every body.

NEF to JPEG Nikon Electric Film can be converted by our online convert tool. Upload your RAW files to our converter and then click convert to finish.
